A Finding Aid to the Emily A. Francis papers, circa 1910s-1969, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1931-1965; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 0.8 Linear feet Box 5
  Exhibitions held at the Contemporary Arts gallery for individual artists and group shows, as well as annual seasonal traveling exhibitions, are included with exhibition files, and contain correspondence, scattered catalogs and announcements, exhibition catalog mock-ups, and exhibition price lists.
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Exhibition Price Lists, 1938-1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Contemporary Arts Exhibition Catalog Mock-Ups, 1938-circa 1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Contemporary Arts Exhibition Price Lists, 1931-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3-5)
  - Figurines, Flowers and Landscapes (Mid-Summer Exhibition) (1939), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Collectors Group Exhibitions (1945), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 57th Street -- Inside and Outside (1950), circa 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The Evening Meal (1951), circa 1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Contemporary Arts 6th Annual Traveling Exhibition (1952-1953), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Contemporary Arts 7th Annual Traveling Exhibition: 25 Paintings by 5 University Art Instructors (1953-1954), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
  - Contemporary Arts 8th Annual Traveling Exhibition (1954-1955), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13-14)
  - Mid-Season Group Exhibition (1955), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Contemporary Arts 9th Annual Traveling Exhibition (1955-1956), 1954-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16-17)
  - Mid-Season Retrospective (1956), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Summer Group Exhibition (1956), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Contemporary Arts 10th Annual Traveling Exhibition (1956-1957), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20-21)
  - 10th Annual Traveling Exhibition: Part II (1957), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22-23)
  - Contemporary Arts 11th Annual Traveling Exhibition (1957-1958), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Contemporary Arts 13th Annual Traveling Exhibition (1959-1960), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25-26)
  - God and Man in Art (1958-1959), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Annual Pre-Season Group Exhibition (1960), 1960-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Brazilian-North American Good-Will Exhibition (1960), 1944-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 29-32)
    Includes correspondence with Antonio Henrique Amaral.
  - Contemporary Arts 14th Annual Traveling Exhibition (1960-1961), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Contemporary Arts 15th Annual Traveling Exhibition (1961-1962), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - First Armed Forces Traveling Exhibition (1962), 1961-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Contemporary Arts 16th Annual Traveling Exhibition (1962-1963), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Group Shows (1963 and 1964), 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Randi Aaroe (1964), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - South America Traveling Exhibition (1965), 1961-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Korean Exhibition, Proposed, 1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - African Exhibition, Proposed, 1963-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Membership Materials, 1935-1966, undated; Series 7; Archival Resource Key; 0.4 Linear feet Boxes 5-6
  Member activities with the Collectors of American Art, Inc. and Contemporary Arts are represented in membership files through draft member letters, member bulletin mock-ups, member reports, membership events, paid memberships, and four membership registers.
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Draft Membership Letters, 1935-circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Forms and Announcements, circa 1938-1944, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Membership Register, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Membership Register ("Collectors 1940"), 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Membership Register ("Collectors 1942"), 1942-1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Membership Register, 1946-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Mock-Ups (Member Letters and Bulletins), 1938-1958, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Monthly Painting Drawings Events, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Paid Memberships, 1953-1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Contemporary Arts, Inc. Member Reports and Announcements, 1935-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Lists (Members, Committees, Guests), 1936-1959, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Business and Financial Material, 1928-1966; Series 8; Archival Resource Key; 1.3 Linear feet Boxes 6-7
  Business and financial materials are comprised of assorted tax and legal documents; gallery leases; tax exemption status documents; financial reports and bank materials; and receipts and invoices. Also included are 17 financial ledgers consisting of sales, artist accounts, petty cash, and general expenses.
  - Charitable Organizations Annual Reports, New York, 1935-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Check Stub Receipt Book, 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Check Stub Receipt Book, 1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Check Stub Receipt Book, 1962-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Contemporary Arts and Collectors of American Art, Inc., Miscellaneous Financial Documents, 1956-circa 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Bank Book, 1938-1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Bank Statements, 1938-1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Donated Print Appraisals, 1962-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Financial Reports, 1939-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Paid Invoices, 1956-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Consignment Invoices ("Artists Invoices"), 1955-1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Contemporary Arts Expenses, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Contemporary Arts Financial Reports, 1931-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Contemporary Arts Leases, 1937-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Contemporary Arts Legal Documents, 1938-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Contemporary Arts Sales and Artist Accounts Ledger, 1949-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Contemporary Arts Sales Invoices, 1958-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Donations for Emily A. Francis' Funeral Expenses, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Financial Ledger, "Accounts Receivable", 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Financial Ledger, Artist/Owner Accounts, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Financial Ledger, "Artist Accounts", 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Financial Ledger, "Artist Accounts", circa 1956-circa 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 30-32)
  - Financial Ledger, "Cash Book", 1929-1934; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Financial Ledger, "Cash Book", 1949-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Financial Ledger, "Collectors of American Art, Inc. Cash Journal No. 1", 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Financial Ledger, "Collectors of American Art, Inc. Cash Journal No. 2", 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Financial Ledger, "Contemporary Arts Ledger" General Ledger, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Financial Ledger, "Contemporary Arts, Inc., General Journal", 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Financial Ledger, "Contemporary Arts Ledger" General Ledger, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Financial Ledger, "Merchandise Purchases and Consignments", 1928-1931; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Financial Ledger, "Petty Cash Book", 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Financial Ledger, Sales Ledger, 1946-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Financial Ledger, General Financial Ledger, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Financial Ledger, General Financial Ledger, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Invoices, 1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Petty Cash Vouchers and Receipts, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7-8)
  - Receipts and Invoices, 1929-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9-13)
  - Tax Exemption Papers, 1948-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Printed Material, 1931-1966, undated; Series 9; Archival Resource Key; 1.3 Linear feet Boxes 7-8
  Printed material includes exhibition catalogs and announcements, annual reports, member's bulletins, "Bulletin of Collectors of American Art, Inc.," event programs, clippings, and press releases.
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Annual Dinner Tickets, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Annual Reports, 1949-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16-19)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. "Bulletin of Collectors of American Art, Inc.", 1938-1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20-21)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Event and Exhibition Announcements, 1938-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22-23)
  - Collectors of American Art, Inc. Member's Bulletins, 1938-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24-26)
  - Contemporary Arts Event Programs, circa 1931-1934, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Contemporary Arts Exhibition Announcements, 1931-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28-31)
  - Contemporary Arts Exhibition Announcements, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Contemporary Arts Exhibition Catalogs, 1931-1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2-16)
  - Contemporary Arts Exhibition Posters, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, Works Loaned by Contemporary Arts, 1933-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, Works Loaned by Contemporary Arts, 1942-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, Works Loaned by Contemporary Arts, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Magazine Clippings, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Magazine Clippings, 1940-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1946-circa 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 24-28)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Brazil Exhibition (Mounted), 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Mounted), 1931-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Periodicals and Newsletters Mentioning Contemporary Arts or Collectors of American Art, Inc., 1948-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Press Releases, 1931-circa 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 32-33)
- Scrapbooks, 1931-1962; Series 10; Archival Resource Key; 1.2 Linear feet Boxes 8-9, 13-14
  Fifteen scrapbooks include clippings; artist pages of exhibition catalogs, announcements, and related clippings; gallery scrapbooks highlighting annual events, activities, and exhibitions throughout the year; and event scrapbooks concerning a 1931 Contemporary Arts costume ball, and the 1951 Emily A. Francis testimonial dinner.
  - Contemporary Arts Scrapbook, 1930-1931; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 34-35)
  - Contemporary Arts Costume Ball Clippings Scrapbook, 1931; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Contemporary Arts "From Kane to Kerkam" Scrapbook, 1931-1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Contemporary Arts Scrapbook, 1931; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Contemporary Arts Scrapbook, Oversized, 1935-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Contemporary Arts Scrapbook, Oversized, 1937-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Contemporary Arts Scrapbook, Oversized, 1944-1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Contemporary Arts Scrapbook, Oversized, 1945-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Contemporary Arts Scrapbook, Oversized, 1945-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Contemporary Arts Scrapbook, Oversized, 1948-1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Contemporary Arts Scrapbook, Oversized, 1949-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Contemporary Arts Scrapbook, Oversized, 1956-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Contemporary Arts Scrapbook, 1956-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Contemporary Arts Traveling Exhibitions Scrapbook, 1957-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Emily A. Francis Testimonial Dinner Scrapbook, 1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Loose Scrapbook Pages, Oversized, circa 1940, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Artwork, 1940-1962, undated; Series 11; Archival Resource Key; 0.9 Linear feet Boxes 10-12
  Artwork is primarily comprised of original prints, including woodcut prints and serigraphs, likely created by artists for the Collectors of American Art, Inc. annual distributions. Also included are a charcoal sketch, paintings, and paint sketches. Artists include Will Barnet, Ben-Zion, Stephen Csoka, Helen Gerardia, José Guerrero, Riva Helfond, Guy Maccoy, Ethel Magafan, Ann Twardowicz, Stanley Twardowicz, and Adja Yunkers, among others.
  - Charcoal Sketch, Marion K. Haldenstein, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Original Prints, Artists A, Oversized, circa 1942-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Includes Ruth Ann and others.
  - Original Prints, Susan Aitkenhead, circa 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Original Prints, Ruth Ann, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Original Prints, Artists B, Oversized, circa 1942-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Includes Will Barnet, Selma Bluestein, and others.
  - Original Prints, Will Barnet, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Original Prints, Ben-Zion, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Original Prints, Jack Bilander, 1951-1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Original Prints, Selma Bluestein, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Original Prints, Artists C, Oversized, circa 1942-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Includes Stephen Csoka and others.
  - Original Prints, Stephen Csoka, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Original Prints, Artists D, Oversized, circa 1942-circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Includes Charles Douglas and others.
  - Original Prints, Charles Douglas, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Original Prints, Artists E-F, Oversized, circa 1942-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Original Prints, E. Espinoza, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Original Prints, Louise A. Freedman, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Original Prints, Artists G, Oversized, circa 1942-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Includes Helen Gerardia, Theodore Gleaves, Bertram Goodman, Elenor S. Greenberg, F. Betty Guerber, and others.
  - Original Prints, Helen Gerardia, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Original Prints, Theodore Gleaves, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Original Prints, Bertram Goodman, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Original Prints, Elenor S. Greenberg, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Original Prints, F. Betty Guerber, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Original Prints, José Guerrero, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Original Prints, Ruth Guinzburg, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Original Prints, Artists H, Oversized, circa 1942-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Includes Riva Helfond and others.
  - Original Prints, Hildegarde Haas, 1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Original Prints, Marion K. Haldenstein, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Original Prints, Miriam Haworth, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Original Prints, Geza Heller, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Original Prints, Riva Helfond, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Original Prints, Artists K, Oversized, circa 1942-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Original Prints, Edna Kaula, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Original Prints, Richard O. Keys, circa 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Original Prints, Artists L, Oversized, circa 1942-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Includes Gail Leff, Rita Leff, and others.
  - Original Prints, Gail Leff, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Original Prints, Rita Leff, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Original Prints, Artists M, Oversized, circa 1942-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key; Includes Guy Maccoy, Ethel Magafan, Tess Manilla, Tobias Musicant, and others. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Original Prints, Guy Maccoy, circa 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Original Prints, Ethel Magafan, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Original Prints, Tess Manilla, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Original Prints, Tobias Musicant, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Original Prints, Lowell Naeve, Oversized, circa 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Original Prints, Nancy Nemec, Oversized, 1960-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Original Prints, Artists O-P, Oversized, circa 1942-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Includes Virginia Paccassi, George Peter, Leonard Pytlak, and others.
  - Original Prints, Virginia Paccassi, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Original Prints, Benton P. Patten, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Original Prints, George Peter, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Original Prints, Leonard Pytlak, circa 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Original Prints, Artists R-S, Oversized, circa 1942-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Includes Helen Siegl and others.
  - Original Prints, Leo Russell, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Original Prints, Helen Siegl, circa 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Original Prints, Iris Simon, circa 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Original Prints, Paul Strisik, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Original Prints, Artists T-Unidentified, Oversized, circa 1942-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Includes Ann Twardowicz and others.
  - Original Prints, Ann Twardowicz, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Original Prints, Stanley Twardowicz, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Original Prints, Louis Tytell, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Original Prints, Unidentified Artists, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Original Prints, Artists V-Y, Oversized, circa 1942-circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Includes Adja Yunkers and others.
  - Original Prints, Karen Weintraub, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Original Prints, Whenfeld, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Original Prints, Adja Yunkers, 1952-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Original Prints, Zenk, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Paintings and Paint Sketches, Oversized, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Includes artists Jean Gunther, De Rosa, and Sadie Rosenblum.
- Photographs, circa 1910s-circa 1960s; Series 12; Archival Resource Key; 0.1 Linear feet Boxes 10, 12
  Photographs include portraits and photographs of Emily A. Francis and others; gallery installation views; John Pellew and other artists at work; and artwork.
  - Emily A. Francis Portrait Photographs, circa 1952-circa 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Photographs of Emily A. Francis with Others, circa 1950-circa 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Vintage Family Photographs, circa 1910s-circa 1920s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Installation Views, Oversized, circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Installation Views, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Event Photographs, circa 1950s-circa 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Photographs of John Pellew and Unidentified Artists Creating Charcoal Sketches, circa 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Photographs of People, Unidentified, circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Photographs of Animals and Outdoors, circa 1940s-circa 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Film Stills, "The Hollywood Revue", circa 1929; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1948, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Photographs of Artwork ("Photographs of Collectors Paintings"), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 57)